let questions=[
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stands for?",
        answer: "C. Hyper Text MarkUp Language",
        options:[
           "A. Hyper Type Multi Language",
           "B. Hyper Text Multiple Language",
           "C. Hyper Text MarkUp Language",
           "D. Home Text Multi Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"What does CSS stands for?",
        answer: "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
        options:[
            "A. Cascading Style Sheet",
            "B. Cute Style Sheet",
            "C. Computer Style Sheet",
            "D. Codehal Style Sheet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"What does PHP stands for?",
        answer: "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
        options:[
            "A. Hypertext Preprocessor",
            "B. HomeText Programming",
            "C. Hypertext Programming",
            "D. Programming Hypertext Preprocessor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"What SQL stands for?",
        answer: "D. Structured Query Language",
        options:[
            "A. Strengthy Query Language",
            "B. Stylesheet Query Language",
            "C. Science Question Language",
            "D. Structured Query Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"What does XML stands for?",
        answer: "D. Extensible Markup Language",
        options:[
            "A. Excellent Multiple Language",
            "B. Explore Multiple Language",
            "C. Extra Markup Language",
            "D. Extensible Markup Language"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"HTML document can contain?",
        answer: "D. All Of These",
        options:[
            "A. Attributes",
            "B. Tags",
            "C. Plain Text",
            "D. All Of These"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"HTML was proposed in year__?",
        answer: "B. 1990",
        options:[
            "A. 1980",
            "B. 1990",
            "C. 1995",
            "D. 2000"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Javascript is an __ language?",
        answer: "A. Object-Oriented",
        options:[
            "A. Object-Oriented",
            "B. Object-Based",
            "C. Procedural",
            "D. None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"switch(expression) { statements  }?",
        answer: "A. ===",
        options:[
            "A. ===",
            "B. equals",
            "C. ==",
            "D. equals"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question:"Which of the following are parts of the CSS box model?",
        answer: "D. All the above",
        options:[
            "A. Margins",
            "B. Paddings",
            "C. Borders",
            "D. All the above"
        ]
    }
]